Some roads lead to murder
Mystery Road is a thriller, crime, drama film directed by Ivan Sen.
A murdered girl is found under a bridge on a remote road and
indigenous detective Jay Swan gets the case.
Jay finds that no-one is that interested in solving the murder of an
indigenous teenager and he is forced to work alone.
Det. Jay Swan, played by Aaron Pedersen.
Johnno, played by Hugo Weaving.
Charlie Murray, played by Jack Thompson.
Pete Barry; William Smith, played by Ryan Kwanten.
Sarge, played by Tony Barry.
Jim, played by Bruce Spence.
Mystery Road is a 2013 Australian crime film with neo-Western
elements and setting, written and directed by Ivan Sen.
It was screened in the Special Presentation section at the
2013 Toronto International Film Festival.
A film sequel entitled Goldstone was released in 2016, and TV series in 2018, all featuring
Aaron Pedersen as the brooding Indigenous Australian detective Jay Swan.
The film explores themes of australia, detective, sniper
rifle, outback, australian aboriginal.
The tone is emotional and intense.